Little Magazine Collection, 1895-1976 (bulk 1965-1976)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Sequoia, Stanford University, Stanford, California, v. 7, #3, Spring, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Sequoia, Stanford University, Stanford, California, v. 21, #1, Summer/Autumn, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Set, Gloucester, Massachusetts, #1, Winter, 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Seventh Street, New York City, Spring, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- The Seventies, Madison, Wisconsin, #7, Winter (THE SIXTIES), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- The Seventies, Madison, Wisconsin, #8, Spring (THE SIXTIES), 1966 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- The Seventies, Madison, Wisconsin, #10, Summer (THE SIXTIES), 1968 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- The Seventies, Madison, Wisconsin, #1, Spring, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Shankpainter, Provincetown, Massachusetts, #1, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- Shankpainter, Provincetown, Massachusetts, #2, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Shantih, New York City, v. 1, #1, Winter, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- Shantih, New York City, v. 1, #2, Summer, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- Shantih, New York City, v. 1, #3, Fall, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 30)
- Shantih, New York City, v. 1, #4, Winter/Spring, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 31)
- Shantih, New York City, v. 2, #2, Summer, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 32)
- Shantih, New York City, v. 2, #4, Spring/Summer, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 33)
- Shell, Waban, Massachusetts, #1, Fall/Winter, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 34)
- Shig's Review, San Francisco, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Shit Sheet, #2, December, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Shocks, San Francisco, #3-4, March, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Shocks, San Francisco, #5, February, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- The Shore Review, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, #1, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- The Shore Review, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, #2-3, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Shuttle, #1, May, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Sibyl-Child, Silver Spring, Maryland, v. 1, #4, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Sibyl-Child, Silver Spring, Maryland, v. 2, #1, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Siglo 1 - Poesia, Mexico, #9, July, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Signal, New York City, v. 1, #1, Fall, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Signal, New York City, v. 1, #2, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Signal, New York City, v. 1, #3, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Signet, Alamo, California, v. 3, #11, November, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Silo, Bennington College, Bennington, Vermont, #8, Fall, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Simbolica, Tiburon, California, #5, undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Simbolica, Tiburon, California, #25, undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Skylight, Didsbury, England, #1, Spring, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Skylight, Didsbury, England, #2, Winter/Spring, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Skywriting, Eugene, Oregon, v. 1, #1, October, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- Small Moon, Boston, Spring, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- The Small Pond, Auburn, Maine, #8, Winter, 1966-1967 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- The Small Pond, Auburn, Maine, #9, Spring, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- The Small Pond, Auburn, Maine, #10, Fall, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- The Small Pond, Auburn, Maine, #11, Winter, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- The Small Pond, Auburn, Maine, #14, Summer, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 26)
- The Small Pond, Auburn, Maine, #15, Winter, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 27)
- The Small Pond, Auburn, Maine, #16, Winter, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 28)
- The Small Pond, Stamford, Connecticut, #17, Fall, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 29)
- Sol, Wivenhoe, England, #3, undated (Box 48, Folder 30)
- Sol Tide, Guadalopita, New Mexico, undated (Box 48, Folder 31)
- Solstice, London, England, #2, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 32)
- Solstice, London, England, #4, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 33)
- Some, New York City, #1, Spring, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 34)
- Some, New York City, #2, Fall, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 35)
- Some, New York City, #3, Winter, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 36)
- Some, New York City, #4, Summer, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 37)
- Some/Thing, New York City, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Some/Thing, New York City, v. 1, #2, Winter, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- South and West, Fort Smith, Arkansas, v. 2, #3, Winter, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- South and West, Fort Smith, Arkansas, v. 3, #3, Winter, 1964-1965 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- South and West, Fort Smith, Arkansas, v. 3, #4, Spring, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- South and West, Fort Smith, Arkansas, v. 6, #4, Spring, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Southern California Lit Scene, Long Beach, California, v. 1, #3, February, 1971-June, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Spanish Fleye, Toronto, Canada, #1, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Sparrow, Flushing, New York, #9, April, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Sparrow, West Lafayette, Indiana, #27, June, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Spectrum, University of California, Santa Barbara, California, v. 10, #1, Spring, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- The Spirit that Moves Us Magazine, Iowa City, Iowa, v. 1, #1, September, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- The Spirit that Moves Us Magazine, Iowa City, Iowa, v. 1, #2, January, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Spring, Idaho State University, Pocatello, Idaho, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Star West, Sausalito, California, v. 1, #1, undated (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Star West, Sausalito, California, v. 1, #5, Summer, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Star West, Sausalito, California, v. 1, #6, November 19, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Stereo Headphones, Kersey, England, #4, Spring, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- The Stone, Pennington, New Jersey, v. 3, #1-2, Winter/Summer, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- The Stone, Ulysses, New York, v. 4, #2-3, Winter (#8-9), 1973 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- The Stone, San Francisco, v. 5 (#10), 1975 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- St(One) Wind, Chicago, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Stooge, Berkeley, California, #1, undated (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Stooge, Berkeley, California, #2, undated (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Stooge, Albuquerque, New Mexico, #6, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Stooge, Los Angeles, #8, March, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Stooge, Berkeley, California, #13, Spring, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Strange Faeces, London, England, #1, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Strange Faeces, London, England, #3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Strange Faeces, London, England, #4, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Strange Faeces, London, England, #8, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Strange Faeces, London, England, #10, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Strange Faeces, London, England, #12-13, April, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Strange Faeces, Oakland, California, #15, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Strange Faeces, Penfield, New York, #17, June, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Strange Faeces, Penfield, New York, #18, November, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Street Magazine, Mastic, New York, v. 1, #4, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Stroker, New York City, #3, Fall, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Structure, Dublin, Ireland, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Stuffed Crocodile, London, Canada, v. 1, #1, February, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Stuffed Crocodile, London, Canada, v. 1, #2, April, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Stuffed Crocodile, London, Canada, v. 1, #3, August, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Stuffed Crocodile, London, Canada, v. 1, #4, November, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Suction, Iowa City, Iowa, v. 1, #1, May, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Suction, Iowa City, Iowa, #2, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Sueños, San Francisco, #1, undated (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Sueños, San Francisco, #2, undated (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Sueños, Los Altos, California, #3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- The Sullivan Slough Review, Edmonds, Washington, #1, Spring, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Sum, Albuquerque, New Mexico, #1, December, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Sum, Albuquerque, New Mexico, #2, February, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Sum, Albuquerque, New Mexico, #3, May, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Sum, Buffalo, New York, #5, April, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 26)
- Sum, Buffalo, New York, #6, April, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 27)
- Sum, Buffalo, New York, #7, April, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Sumus, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, #1, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 29)
- Sun, New York City, v. 3, #2-3, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Sunbury, New York City, v. 1, #1, April, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Sunshine, New York City, May, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Sunyata, Montreal, Canada, #1, Winter, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Sweep, Brooklyn, New York, v. 1, #2, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Swing, New York City, #1, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Swing, New York City, #2, Spring, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Swing, New York City, #3, Summer, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Swing, New York City, #4, Fall, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Synapse, Berkeley, California, #1, undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Synapse, Berkeley, California, #4, May, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Synapse, University of California, Irvine, California, v. 2, #1, Autumn, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Tabloid Story, Glebe, Australia, #17, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Talon, Vancouver, Canada, v. 4, #2, undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Talon, Vancouver, Canada, v. 4, #3, undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Talon, Vancouver, Canada, v. 5, #1, undated (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Talud, Venezuela, v. 2, #3, March, 1970-April, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Talud, Venezuela, v. 2, #4, May, 1970-August, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Talud, Venezuela, v. 2, #5, September, 1970-May, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Tam Tam, Italy, #3-4, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Tansy, Lawrence, Kansas, #2, undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Tar River Poets, East Carolina University, Greenville, North Carolina, #7, undated (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Tar River Poets, East Carolina University, Greenville, North Carolina, #8, undated (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Tar River Poets, East Carolina University, Greenville, North Carolina, #9, undated (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Tar River Poets, East Carolina University, Greenville, North Carolina, #11, Winter, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Tar River Poets, East Carolina University, Greenville, North Carolina, #16, Spring, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Telephone, New York City, #2, undated (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Telephone, New York City, #3, undated (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Telephone, New York City, #4, undated (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Telephone, New York City, #5, undated (Box 51, Folder 30)
- Telephone, New York City, #6, Spring, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Telephone, New York City, #7, Fall, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Telephone, New York City, #12, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- the, Boulder, Colorado, #3, undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
- the, Boulder, Colorado, #5, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- the, Boulder, Colorado, #6, undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
- the, Boulder, Colorado, #7, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
- the, Boulder, Colorado, #8, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
- the, Boulder, Colorado, #9, undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
- the, Boulder, Colorado, #10, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Theo, Utica, New York, #3, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- things, New York City, #1, Fall, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- 13th Moon, New York City, v. 2, #2 through v. 3, #1, Winter, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- this, Iowa City, Iowa; Glouster, Massachusetts, #1, Winter, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- this, Iowa City, Iowa; Franconia, New Hampshire, #2, Fall, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- this, Oakland, California; Franconia New Hampshire, #3, Fall, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- this, San Francisco; Franconia, New Hampshire, #4, Spring, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- this, San Francisco; Franconia, New Hampshire, #5, Winter, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- this, San Francisco, #6, Spring, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- This and..., New York City, #11, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 19)
- This and..., New York City, #12, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 20)
- 3¢ Pulp, Vancouver, Canada, v. 2, #6, April 15, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 21)
- 3¢ Pulp, Vancouver, Canada, v. 2, #9, June 15, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 22)
- 3¢ Pulp, Vancouver, Canada, v. 2, #17, November 15, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 23)
- Tin-Tan, San Francisco, v. 1, #1, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 24)
- The Tiresian, Tulane University, New Orleans, v. 2, #1, Fall, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 25)
- Titmouse, Vancouver, Canada, v. 1, #1, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 26)
- Titmouse, Vancouver, Canada, v. 1, #2, Winter, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 27)
- Titmouse, Vancouver, Canada, #3, Summer, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 28)
- Titmouse, Vancouver, Canada, #4, Spring, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 29)
- Titmouse, Vancouver, Canada, #5, Winter, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 30)
- Titmouse, Vancouver, Canada, #6, Summer/Fall, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 31)
- Tlaloc, Leeds, England, #14, undated (Box 52, Folder 32)
- Tlaloc, London, England, #17, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 33)
- Tlaloc, London, England, #21, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 34)
- Today, Chicago, v. 21, #1, October, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 35)
- The Tolar Creek Syndicate, Las Cruces, New Mexico, v. 1, #3, July, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 36)
- The Tolar Creek Syndicate, Las Cruces, New Mexico, v. 1, #4, December, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 37)
- The Tolar Creek Syndicate, Las Cruces, New Mexico, v. 1, #6, May, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 38)
- The Tolar Creek Syndicate, Las Cruces, New Mexico, v. 1, #7, April, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 39)
- The Tolar Creek Syndicate, Las Cruces, New Mexico, v. 1, #8, September, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 40)
- The Tolar Creek Syndicate, Las Cruces, New Mexico, v. 1, #9, August, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 41)
- Tom Veitch Magazine, San Francisco, #1, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 42)
- Tom Veitch Magazine, San Francisco, #2, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 43)
- Tom Veitch Magazine, San Francisco, #3, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 44)
- Tom Veitch Magazine, San Francisco, #4, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 45)
- Toothpaste, Iowa City, Iowa, #1, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Toothpaste, Iowa City, Iowa, #2, November, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Toothpaste, Iowa City, Iowa, #3, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Toothpaste, Iowa City, Iowa, #4, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Toothpaste, Iowa City, Iowa, #5, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Toothpaste, Iowa City, Iowa, #6, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Toothpaste, Iowa City, Iowa, #7, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Toothpick, Lisbon & the Orcas Islands, Seattle, #1, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Toothpick, Lisbon & the Orcas Islands, Seattle, v. 2, #1-2, Fall (#3), 1972 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- total, West Germany, v. 4, #13, undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Tottel's, Oakland, California, #8, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Tottel's, Oakland, California, #15, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Toucan, Kent, Ohio, v. 1, #2, Winter, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Toucan, Kent, Ohio, v. 2, #2-3, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Touchstone, v. 4, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Transfer, San Francisco State College, San Francisco, #10, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Transfer, San Francisco State College, San Francisco, #11, undated (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Transfer, San Francisco State College, San Francisco, #18, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- Transfer, San Francisco State College, San Francisco, #19, May, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Transfer, San Francisco State College, San Francisco, #20, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Transpacific, Laport, Colorado, #1, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Transpacific, Yellow Springs, Ohio, #3, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- Transpacific, Yellow Springs, Ohio, v. 1, #4, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- Transpacific, Yellow Springs, Ohio, v. 2, #1 (#5), 1970 (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Transpacific, Yellow Springs, Ohio, v. 2, #2 (#6), 1971 (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Transpacific, Yellow Springs, Ohio, v. 2, #3 (#7), 1971 (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Transpacific, Yellow Springs, Ohio, v. 2, #4 (#8), 1971 (Box 53, Folder 27)
- Tree, Bolinas, California, #1, Winter, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Tree, Bolinas, California, #2, Summer, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Tree, Bolinas, California, #3, Winter, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- La Trenza, Argentina, #1, July, 1968-August, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- La Trenza, Argentina, #8-9, January, 1970-June, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- The Triangle, Illinois State University, Normal, Illinois, v. 7, September, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Tropico Uno, Venezuela, #4, November, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Tuatara, Victoria, Canada, #1, Fall, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Tuatara, Victoria, Canada, #5, July, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Tuatara, Victoria, Canada, #6, November, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Tuatara, Victoria, Canada, #7, Spring, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Tuatara, Victoria, Canada, #8-9, Fall, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Turtle, London, England, #2, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Typewriter, Iowa City, Iowa, #2, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- 12th Street, New School for Social Research, New York City, v. 3, #1, December, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Two Charlies Magazine, Alameda, New Mexico; Scappose, Oregon, #2, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Tzarad, London, England, #1, August, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Umbra/Blackworks, New York City, Summer, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Umbrella, Coventry, England, v. 1, #4, Autumn, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Umbrella, Coventry, England, v. 2, #5, Spring, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Umbrella, Coventry, England, v. 2, #6, Autumn, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Umbrella, Coventry, England, v. 2, #7, Spring, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Umbrella, Coventry, England, v. 2, #8, Summer, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Underdog, Liverpool, England, #8, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 24)
- the undermine press, New York City, #1, undated (Box 54, Folder 25)
- the undermine press, New York City, #2, undated (Box 54, Folder 26)
- the undermine press, New York City, #3, undated (Box 54, Folder 27)
- up the tube with one i (open), Stepworth Burnaby, Canada, #4, undated (Box 54, Folder 28)
- Vagabond, Redwood City, California, #14, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 29)
- Vagabond, Redwood City, California, #16, November, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 30)
- Vagabond, Ellensburg, Washington, #18, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 31)
- Vagabond, Ellensburg, Washington, #19, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 32)
- Vagabond, Ellensburg, Washington, #20, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 33)
- Vagabond, Ellensburg, Washington, #22, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 34)
- Vagabond, Munich, West Germany (German Edition), #1, July, 1967-September, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 35)
- Variegation, Los Angeles, v. 5, #1, Winter, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Via, University of California, Berkeley, California, #1, May, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Viewpoints in Focus, New York City, December, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Vigilante, Calgary, Canada, #1, May, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- The Village Idiot, Santa Barbara, California, #2, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- The Village Idiot, Santa Barbara, California, #3, April, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Virgin, New York City, #1, September, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Virtue, Buffalo, New York, May, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Voices, New York City, #137, Spring, 1949 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Voices, New York City, #141, Spring, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Vole, Hitchin, England, #2, undated (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Volume 63, University of Waterloo, Canada, v. 63, #1, December, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Volume 63, University of Waterloo, Canada, v. 63, #3, Summer, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Vort, Silver Spring, Maryland, #1, Fall, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Vort, Silver Spring, Maryland, #2, Winter, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Voyages, Washington, D.C., v. 2, #1-2, Winter/Spring, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Voyages, Washington, D.C., v. 2, #3, Fall, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Voyages, Washington, D.C., v. 2, #4, Spring, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Wagner Literary Magazine, Wagner College, Staten Island, New York, #3, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Wagtail, Sarnia, Canada, #1, April, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Wagtail, Sarnia, Canada, #3, Winter, 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Wasatch Front, University of Utah, Salt Lake City, v. 58, #1, Winter, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Wasatch Front, University of Utah, Salt Lake City, v. 58, #2, Spring, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Wasatch Front, University of Utah, Salt Lake City, v. 58 (The Best of Wasatch Front), 1970 (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Washout Review, Schenectady, New York, v. 1, #3, undated (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Waste Paper, Shibpur, India, #4, September, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 26)
- Waste Paper, Shibpur, India, #5, July, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 27)
- Wave, Hull, England, #5, Autumn, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 28)
- Weapon, New York City; Oakland, California, #1, Fall/Winter, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 29)
- Weed, Kitchener, Canada, #2, March, 1966-April, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 30)
- Weed, Kitchener, Canada, #4, July, 1966-August, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 31)
- Weed, Kitchener, Canada, #6, November, 1966-December, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 32)
- Weed, Kitchener, Canada, #7, January, 1967-February, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 33)
- Weed, Kitchener, Canada, #8, March, 1967-April, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 34)
- Weed, Kitchener, Canada, #9, May, 1967-June, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 35)
- Weed, Kitchener, Canada, #10, July, 1967-August, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 36)
- Weed, Kitchener, Canada, #12, November, 1967-December, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 37)
- Weid, Homestead, Florida, v. 11, #1-3 (#42-43), September, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- West Coast Poetry Review, Reno, Nevada, v. 3, #2, Winter (#10), 1973 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- West Coast Poetry Review, Reno, Nevada, v. 3, #3, Spring (#11), 1974 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- West Coast Poetry Review, Reno, Nevada, v. 4, #1-2, Fall (#13-14), 1974 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- West Coast Poetry Review, Reno, Nevada, v. 4, #3, Winter (#15), 1974 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- West Coast Poetry Review, Reno, Nevada, v. 5, #1 (#17), 1976 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- West End, New York City, v. 1, #1, Winter, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- West End, New York City, v. 1, #2, Spring/Summer, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- West End, New York City, v. 1, #4, Spring, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- West End, New York City, v. 2, #1, Summer, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- The Western Gate, Buffalo, New York, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Westigan Review of Poetry, Salt Lake City, v. 3, #3 (#11), 1977 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- What Now?, Long Beach City College, Long Beach, California, v. 1, #1, May, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- whe're, Toronto, Canada, #1, Summer, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Whetstone, Huntsville, Texas, v. 5, #2, Fall, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- White Arms Magazine, Fort Wayne, Indiana, #1, April, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- White Arms Magazine, Fort Wayne, Indiana, #2, November, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- The White Elephant, Oakland, California, #2, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- White Pine, Buffalo, New York, #4, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- White Pine, Buffalo, New York, #11, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- The Windless Orchard, Fort Wayne, Indiana, #3, November, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 21)
- The Windless Orchard, Fort Wayne, Indiana, #9, Spring, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- The Windless Orchard, Fort Wayne, Indiana, #10, Summer, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- The Window, London, England, v. 1, #4, October, 1930 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Winged Purposes, Lincoln Center, Massachusetts, v. 1, #1, Fall/Winter, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Wings, Mill Valley, California, v. 6, #5, Spring, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Wisconsin Poetry Magazine, Wauwatosa, Wisconsin, v. 3, #5, May, 1958-June, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Wisconsin Review, University of Wisconsin, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 3, #2, Spring, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Wisconsin Review, University of Wisconsin, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 4, #3, Spring, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Wisconsin Review, University of Wisconsin, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 5, #3, Spring, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Wisconsin Review, University of Wisconsin, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 6, #1, Fall, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Wisconsin Review, University of Wisconsin, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 7, #1, Fall, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Wisconsin Review, University of Wisconsin, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 7, #2, Spring, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Wisconsin Review, University of Wisconsin, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 7, #3, Summer, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Wisconsin Review, University of Wisconsin, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 8, #2, undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
- The Wivenhoe Park Review, Colchester, England, #2, undated (Box 57, Folder 13)
- The Wivenhoe Park Review, Colchester, England, #3 (and The Park 1), 1968 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Wordjock, West Lafayette, Indiana, v. 1, #1, September, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Wordjock, West Lafayette, Indiana, v. 1, #2, February, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 16)